mapchart.net 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - MapChart

### Your privacy is critically important to us.

It is MapChart's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [MapChart](https://mapchart.net/) (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "MapChart"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, MapChart collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MapChart's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MapChart's visitors use its website. From time to time, MapChart may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Advertisements

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MapChart and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Aggregated Statistics

MapChart may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. MapChart may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, MapChart does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

## Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, MapChart may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MapChart's sole discretion. MapChart encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via [email](mailto:contact@mapchart.net).
